Guide to the Montana Department of Environmental Quality, Director's Office records 1908-2002
Montana Historical Society
- Subject Files
  - Alcohol and Drug Dependence Commission, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 23/6)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 23/7)
  - Child Care Council of Greater Helena, Community Coordinated Child Care (“4 C’s Program”), 1970 (Box-folder 23/8)
  - Camps State Committee, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 23/9)
  - Civil Defense Advisory Council (incl. Flood Response Report, 1964), 1962-1970 (Box-folder 23/10)
  - Commission on Aging (incl. Older Americans Act, State Plan for Implementation), 1965 (Box-folder 23/11)
  - Community Mental Health Advisory Board, 1955-1969 (Box-folder 23/12)
  - Emergency Hospitals, 1962-1970 (Box-folder 23/13)
  - Joint Staff Committee, 1952-1970 (Box-folder 23/14)
  - Medical Assistance Advisory Council, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 23/15)
  - Medical Self-Help, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 23/16)
  - Migrant Health (incl. “Migrant Health Proposal”), 1969-1971 (Box-folder 23/17)
  - Model Cities, Butte, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 23/18)
  - Model Cities, Helena, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 23/19)
  - Montana Family Planning (incl. “Male Demonstration Projects” Grant Application), 1978 (Box-folder 23/20)
  - Montana Health Planning Council, 1959 (Box-folder 23/21)
  - Montana Manpower Planning Advisory Council, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 23/22)
  - Montana Wildlife Federation, 1969 (Box-folder 23/23)
  - CTSH, General Information, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 24/10)
  - ADA Information, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 24/11)
  - “CMG/MHAP Info and Updates”, 1996 (Box-folder 24/12)
  - “Caring Program for Children”, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 24/13)
  - DHES/DPHHS, Press Releases, 1995 (Box-folder 24/14)
  - “Flood/Emergencies Info”, 1997 (Box-folder 24/15)
  - Food and Nutrition, 1995 (Box-folder 24/16)
  - “Legislative Session Info”, 1997 (Box-folder 24/17)
  - “METNET”, 1997 (Box-folder 24/18)
  - “One-stop Career Center Planning”, 1995 (Box-folder 24/19)
  - Social and Rehabilitation Services, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 24/20)
  - Social Services Advisory Committee, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 24/21)
  - Vocational Rehabilitation, 1971 (Box-folder 24/22)
  - “Eruption of Mt. St. Helens, DHES Involvement”, 1980 (Box-folder 25/1)
  - “Executive Planning Process, Six Year Plan, 1976 (Box-folder 25/2)
  - Energy Division, 1982 (Box-folder 25/3)
  - Interagency Pipeline Task Force (IPTF), 1980-1982 (Box-folder 25/4)
  - “Intertie” (High voltage transmission line), 1983-1984 (Box-folder 25/5)
  - Kootenai Falls, Advisory Committee, 1980 (Box-folder 25/6)
  - Kootenai Falls, Hydroelectric Dam project, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 25/7)
  - Kootenai Falls, Northern Lights, 1983 (Box-folder 25/8)
  - “Libby Rereg. Dam”, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 25/9)
  - “Legislative Audit Report”, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 25/10)
  - “Notice of Amendment of Certificate, Broadview– Grass Range – Glengarry 100kV line”, 1979 (Box-folder 25/11)
  - “Montana Power Company – Judith Cap – Glengarry 100 kV Transmission Facility (includes Environmental Impact Statement), 1985 (Box-folder 25/12)
  - Northern Border Pipeline Company, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 25/13)
  - Northern Tier Pipeline, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 25/14)
  - Press Releases, 1975-1993 (Box-folder 25/15-17)
  - Comprehensive Environmental Clean-up and Responsibility Act (CECRA), 1986-1992 (Box-folder 26/1)
  - CECRA, Bohrman’s Exxon (Ennis), 1991 (Box-folder 26/2)
  - CECRA, Comet Oil (Billings), 1991 (Box-folder 26/3)
  - CECRA, Gallatin County Asbestos, 1990 (Box-folder 26/4)
  - CECRA, Geraldine Fuel Leak, 1990 (Box-folder 26/5)
  - CECRA, Hart Oil Refinery (Missoula), 1992 (Box-folder 26/6)
  - CECRA, Lima Railroad Site, 1991 (Box-folder 26/7)
  - CECRA, Libby Mine Barrel Site, 1992 (Box-folder 26/8)
  - CECRA, Montana Power Company (Montana St., Butte), 1991 (Box-folder 26/9)
  - CECRA, Nellie Grant Mine, 1991 (Box-folder 26/10)
  - CECRA, Pacific Hide and Fur, 1991 (Box-folder 26/11)
  - CECRA, Precious Metals Plating site (Bonner), 1990 (Box-folder 26/12)
  - CECRA, Shelby Petroleum Refinery, 1991 (Box-folder 26/13)
  - CECRA, Texaco Refinery (Sunburst), 1988-1993 (Box-folder 26/14)
  - CECRA, Donahue Ranch (Wilsall PCB site), 1991 (Box-folder 26/15)
  - CECRA, Yale Oil Company, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 26/16)
  - Environmental Enforcement History, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 26/17)
  - Environmental Restoration and Remediation Policy, 1989 (Box-folder 26/18)
  - Environmental Remediation, L.U.S.T. (Underground Storage Tanks), 1989-1995 (Box-folder 26/19)
  - Oil Overcharge Applications, 1990 (Box-folder 26/20)
  - Pony, Chicago Mining Company (includes Environmental Assessment, Water Quality Bureau), 1989-1991 (Box-folder 26/21)
  - Solid and Hazardous Waste Bureau (SHWB), 1989-1994 (Box-folder 26/22)
  - SHWB, Ash Grove (HW Burning/Cement Kilns) (Box-folder 26/23)
  - SHWB, AJ’s Laundry (Missoula), 1995 (Box-folder 26/24)
  - SHWB, Broadwater County Hazardous Waste Spills, 1986 (Box-folder 26/25)
  - SHWB, Burlington-Northern (Paradise, Whitefish, And Other Sites), 1989-1992 (Box-folder 26/26)
  - SHWB, “Cut Bank Emergency”, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 26/27)
  - SHWB, EPA, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 26/28)
  - SHWB, Integrated Waste Management Plan, 1993 (Box-folder 26/29)
  - SHWB, Landfills, 1987-1995 (Box-folder 26/30)
  - SHWB, Montana Rail Link Derailment, 1989 (Box-folder 26/31)
  - SHWB, “Private Sector Involvement with Proposed HW Collection/Transfer Station, undated (Box-folder 26/32)
  - SHWB, Resource Indemnity Trust (Berkeley Pit), 1986 (Box-folder 26/33)
  - SHWB, Trident Cement Plant, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 26/34)
  - SHWB, “Waste Capacity Assurance Position Paper, 1988 (Box-folder 26/35)
  - Small Scale Hydropower, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 26/36)
  - Staff Meetings, 1980 (Box-folder 26/37)
  - Transcisco Rail Service (TRS), 1994 (Box-folder 26/38)
  - Tribal Jurisdiction (TAS), 1994-1995 (Box-folder 26/39)
  - Tribal Environmental Issues, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 26/40)
  - Tribal Negotiation, Underground Storage Tanks, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 26/41)
  - EPA, Mill Creek, 1986 (Box-folder 27/1)
  - EPA, RCRA Renewal, 1986 (Box-folder 27/2)
  - Functional Organization/Reorganization of ESD, 1994 (Box-folder 27/3)
  - Livingston, Gasoline Spill, 1987 (Box-folder 27/4)
  - Mill Creek, Consent Decree, 1988 (Box-folder 27/5)
  - Mill Creek, Remedial Investigation/Feasibility Study (includes “Superfund Basics…in Montana, 1983 – 1993”), 1986 (Box-folder 27/6)
  - Missoula White Pine Sash (mill site), 1994-1996 (Box-folder 27/7)
  - Multitech Budget Adjustment, 1986 (Box-folder 27/8)
  - Superfund, General Info (Box-folder 27/9)
  - Superfund, Butte (Butte Hill, Travona Shaft West Camp, Wells), 1986-1994 (Box-folder 27/10)
  - Superfund, East Helena (Air Quality, Garden Vegetables, Smelter Study), 1984-1995 (Box-folder 27/11)
  - Superfund, Idaho Pole, 1992 (Box-folder 27/12)
  - Superfund, Kevin (Big West Oil Refinery) (Box-folder 27/13)
  - Superfund, Champion International Corp., 1989-1990 (Box-folder 27/14)
  - Superfund, Mill Creek (Anaconda), 1986 (Box-folder 27/15)
  - Superfund, Mill Creek Remedial Investigation, 1986 (Box-folder 27/16)
  - Superfund, Milltown (Reservoir, Dam), 1985-1995 (Box-folder 27/17)
  - Superfund, Montana Pole, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 27/18)
  - Superfund, Silver Bow Creek (Clark Fork River Fish Kill), 1988-1995 (Box-folder 27/19)
  - Superfund, Sunburst/Timber (Abandoned refinery), 1989 (Box-folder 27/20)
  - ARCO Coal Company (includes: Mill Town Res., Montana Pole, Rocker Arsenic removal, East Helena, Anaconda, Warm Springs Ponds), 1989-1993 (Box-folder 28/1-8)
  - ASARCO (includes: Upper Blackfoot Mining Complex, East Helena, Rock Creek Mine), 1984-1994 (Box-folder 28/9-11)
  - Asbestos in Schools (EPA pub.), 1979 (Box-folder 28/12)
  - Air Quality Bureau, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 28/13)
  - Burlington-Northern (includes: clean-up at various Sites, fueling sites, Whitefish), 1989-1993 (Box-folder 28/14-16)
  - EPA Mid-year Review, 1994 (Box-folder 28/17)
  - Express Pipeline Project, 1993 (Box-folder 28/18)
  - Livingston Rebuild Center/Montana Rail Link, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 28/19)
  - Montana Environmental Info. Center v. DHES (re: Destruction of EPA letter), 1994 (Box-folder 28/20)
  - MEPA Rules, proposed changes, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 28/21)
  - Northern Plains Resource Council, 1995 (Box-folder 28/22)
  - Occupational and Radiological Health Bureau, 1985-1994 (Box-folder 28/23)
  - Superfund, Audits/Reauthorization, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 28/24)
  - Superfund, General, 1986-1995 (Box-folder 28/25)
  - Superfund, Anaconda, 1988-1994 (Box-folder 28/26)
  - Superfund, Butte Lead, 1993 (Box-folder 28/27)
  - Superfund, ESE Appeal, 1994 (Box-folder 28/28)
  - Superfund, Wal-mart (Kalispell), 1993-1994 (Box-folder 28/29)
  - Air Quality Bureau (includes: Forest Fires of Yellowstone County, Stauffer Chemical), 1979-1994 (Box-folder 29/1-6 1988,)
  - ASARCO, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 29/7)
  - Billings Generation Inc., 1992-1993 (Box-folder 29/8)
  - Billings SIP (State Implementation Plan) for Sulfur Dioxide (SO2), 1989-1996 (Box-folder 29/9)
  - Bonneville Power Administration Transmission Line (Spokane-Garrison-Townsend, Libby and Hungry Horse Dams), 1982-1994 (Box-folder 29/10-11)
  - Burlington-Northern, Livingston, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 29/12)
  - Centennial Cattle Drive, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 29/13)
  - DHES v. Church Universal and Triumphant (CUT) (re: Fallout and bomb shelters), 1989-1994 (Box-folder 29/14-16)
  - Helena Sewage Treatment Plant, 1995 (Box-folder 29/17)
  - Land Use Law (Melda), 1976 (Box-folder 29/18)
  - Pony Mine/Mill, 1990 (Box-folder 29/19)
  - Right to Know Law, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 29/20)
  - Small Business Assistance Program (re: Clean Air Act), 1994 (Box-folder 29/21)
  - State Implementation Plans (Kalispell, Libby, Missoula), 1989-1994 (Box-folder 29/22)
  - Stone Container Corporation litigation (includes: Testimony and Hearing Transcripts), 1994-1995 (Box-folder 29/23)
  - Air Quality, Livingston Rail Yard, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 30/10)
  - Burlington-Northern, Response Costs (Underground Storage Tanks), 1990-1991 (Box-folder 30/11)
  - Burlington-Northern, Livingston Clean-up, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 30/12)
  - Church Universal and Triumphant, Weekly/Monthly Summaries, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 30/13)
  - Church Universal and Triumphant, Draft Supplemental Environmental Impact Statement, 1992 (Box-folder 30/14)
  - Environmental Services Division (Don Willems), 1985-1986 (Box-folder 31/1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1984-1992 (Box-folder 31/2)
  - Natural Resource Damage Program (NRDP), 1988-1995 (Box-folder 31/3-10)
  - NRDP, Clark Fork River Basin, 1987, 1993 (Box-folder 31/11-12)
  - Burlington-Northern (BN), Contract Services (John Larson), 1989-1993 (Box-folder 31/13)
  - BN, Livingston, 1988-1993 (Box-folder 31/14-15)
  - BN, “Mission Wye”, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 31/16)
  - BN, “Other Sites”, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 31/17)
  - Church Universal, (Mol Heron site, Media Contract), 1990-1992 (Box-folder 31/18-19)
  - Missoula, California Street, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 31/20)
  - Public Water Supply (PWS) Rule Amendments, 1991 (Box-folder 31/21)
  - SHWB, Yearly Quality Assurance/Quality Control, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 31/22)
  - Burlington-Northern (BN), Monthly Status Reports, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 32/1)
  - BN, Livingston (Rail yard clean-up) (includes Vapor Extraction Report), 1991-1993 (Box-folder 32/2-5)
  - Champion International Stone Container Corp. (includes Environmental Impact Statement), 1992 (Box-folder 32/6)
  - Clark Fork River Basin Project, 1984, 1994 (Box-folder 32/7)
  - Crown Butte Mining, New World Project, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 32/8)
  - Flathead Basin Commission, 1993 (Box-folder 32/9)
  - Water Quality (WQ), ASARCO Troy Mine, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 32/10)
  - WQ, “Audit”, 1994 (Box-folder 32/11)
  - WQ, Big Sky Moratorium, 1985-1995 (Box-folder 32/12)
  - WQ, Billings (City of), 1994 (Box-folder 32/13)
  - WQ, Boehm, Edward (Livingston), 1989 (Box-folder 32/14)
  - WQ, Bozeman (Alderson Street Condos), 1994 (Box-folder 32/15)
  - WQ, Bozeman (Solvent site), 1992-1995 (Box-folder 32/16)
  - WQ, Butte (Water Company), 1989-1994 (Box-folder 32/17)
  - WQ, Cascade (water supply), 1994 (Box-folder 32/18)
  - WQ, Cut Bank (oil seep), 1988 (Box-folder 32/19)
  - WQ, Eastview Homeowners, Boil Water Order (Missoula), 1994 (Box-folder 32/20)
  - WQ, Georgetown Lake, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 32/21)
  - WQ, Hot Springs regulations, 1994 (Box-folder 32/22)
  - WQ, Lindbergh Lake/Herrick Run, 1989 (Box-folder 32/23)
  - WQ, Lockwood Water Users, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 32/24)
  - WQ, Miles City (Richard Buslett), 1979-1990 (Box-folder 32/25)
  - WQ, Miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 32/26)
  - WQ, Chicago Mining Corp, Application for Groundwater Pollution Control (includes sound recording), 1989-1994 (Box-folder 33/1-3)
  - WQ, Mines and Mining, Golden Maple Mining and Leaching, 1986 (Box-folder 33/4)
  - WQ, Mines and Mining, Golden Sunlight Mine, 1994 (Box-folder 33/5)
  - WQ, Mines and Mining, Stillwater Mining, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 33/6)
  - WQ, Miscellaneous, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 33/7-10)
  - WQ, Missoula, 1986 (Box-folder 33/11)
  - WQ, News/Media, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 33/12)
  - WQ, “Non-degradation”, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 33/13-14)
  - WQ, Noranda Minerals (includes Montanore Project), 1990-1992 (Box-folder 33/15-16)
  - WQ, Petroleum Tank Release Compensation Board, 1989 (Box-folder 33/17)
  - WQ, Pondera Hutterite Colony, 1993 (Box-folder 33/18)
  - WQ, Pinesdale, 1995 (Box-folder 33/19)
  - WQ, Ruby River, 1994 (Box-folder 33/20)
  - WQ, Seeley Lake Water District, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 33/21)
  - WQ, State Water Plan Advisory Council, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 33/22)
  - WQ, Subdivisions, Bull Lake Estates, 1994 (Box-folder 33/23)
  - WQ, Subdivisions, Cascade (Big Sky, MT), 1995 (Box-folder 33/24)
  - WQ, Subdivisions, Kinnikinnick Resort (Whitefish), 1995 (Box-folder 33/25)
  - WQ, Subdivisions, Mariner’s Haven, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 33/26)
  - WQ, Subdivisions, O’Brien Creek (Missoula), 1993 (Box-folder 33/27)
  - WQ, Subdivisions, Oxbow (Fuchs), 1993-1995 (Box-folder 33/28)
  - WQ, Subdivisions, Summer Ridge (Gallatin Co.), 1993 (Box-folder 33/29)
  - WQ, Transcript of Hearing (Colstrip 3 and 4), 1978, 1989 (Box-folder 34/1-2)
  - WQ, Whitefish Sewer System, 1995 (Box-folder 34/3)
  - WQ, Zortman, Landusky Mine, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 34/4)
  - Air Rules Amendments, 1976 (Box-folder 34/5)
  - “Briefing Meeting”, 1989 (Box-folder 34/6)
  - Butte-Silver Bow Audit, 1988 (Box-folder 34/7)
  - “Clean Air Act of Montana and Rules”, 1984, 1988 (Box-folder 34/8)
  - DHES Transition Paper and Org chart, 1987 (Box-folder 34/9)
  - Health Officers Meeting, 1981 (Box-folder 34/10)
  - Health Care Service Providers, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 34/11)
  - Human Services Task Force, 1987 (Box-folder 34/12)
  - Library Committee, 1986 (Box-folder 34/13)
  - “Mental Health Patients in Jail” (W. Storli, Kalispell), 1987-1989 (Box-folder 34/14)
  - Montana Central Tumor Registry Advisory Council, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 34/15)
  - Monthly Department Meetings, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 34/16)
  - Water Quality Act and Rules, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 34/17)
  - Anaconda Aluminum, Application for Variance (includes Exhibits, Transcripts, Discovery documents, Findings of Fact, and Court Rulings), 1973-1974 (Box-folder 34/18-23)
- Subject Files
  - Anaconda Aluminum, Variance (Findings, Transcripts), 1974, 1977 (Box-folder 35/1)
  - Anaconda Aluminum, Court Action, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 35/2)
  - Anaconda Aluminum, Deposition (Donald Henderson), 1974 (Box-folder 35/3)
  - Anaconda Aluminum, Final Control Plan, 1975 (Box-folder 35/4)
  - Anaconda Aluminum, Fluoride and Particulates, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 35/5-6)
  - Anaconda Aluminum, Hearings (Declaratory, Rules), 1974-1975 (Box-folder 35/7)
  - Anaconda Aluminum, Pleadings, 1974 (Box-folder 35/8)
  - Anaconda Aluminum, Renewal of Variance, 1975 (Box-folder 35/9)
  - Anaconda Aluminum, Transcripts, 1974 (Box-folder 35/10)
  - Anaconda Aluminum, Application for Variance, Sulfur Oxide emissions (Exhibits and Transcripts), 1974 (Box-folder 35/11-18)
  - Anaconda Aluminum, Application for Variance, Sulfur Oxide emissions (Discovery, Pleadings, Public Comments), 1974-1975 (Box-folder 36/1-3)
  - Board of Health, Miscellaneous (D. Pizzini), 1989-1990 (Box-folder 36/4-5)
  - Compliance Orders, Water Supply Systems, 1991 (Box-folder 36/6)
  - Findings of Fact and Conclusions of Law (FFCL), Church Universal, 1991 (Box-folder 36/7)
  - FFCL, Meadow Gold Dairies, 1991 (Box-folder 36/8)
  - FFCL, Montana Rail Link spill, Sanders Co., 1991 (Box-folder 36/9)
  - Investigation, Clean-up and Compliance, ASARCO, 1991 (Box-folder 36/10)
  - Investigation and Removal of Hazardous Substances, Buttrey’s Shopping Center (Bozeman), 1991 (Box-folder 36/11)
  - Notice of Violation (NOV), ASARCO, 1990 (Box-folder 36/12)
  - NOV, Browning (Town of), 1990 (Box-folder 36/13)
  - NOV, Burlington-Northern (tie plant, Paradise), 1991 (Box-folder 36/14)
  - NOV, Cut Bank (Town of), 1989 (Box-folder 36/15)
  - NOV, Development Corp. (Veradale, WA), 1990 (Box-folder 36/16)
  - NOV, Fromberg (Town of), 1990 (Box-folder 36/17)
  - NOV, Gallatin Field Airport (Belgrade), 1990 (Box-folder 36/18)
  - NOV, Malmstrom AFB, Dept. of Defense, 1991 (Box-folder 36/19)
  - NOV, Moore’s Truck Stop (Shelby), 1991 (Box-folder 36/20)
  - NOV, Northern Montana College, 1991 (Box-folder 36/21)
  - NOV, Stone Container Corp., 1991 (Box-folder 36/22)
  - NOV, Sunbird Aviation (Gallatin Field Airport), 1991 (Box-folder 36/23)
  - Order, State of Montana v. Burlington Northern, 1990 (Box-folder 36/24)
  - Order for Investigation and Clean-up of Asbestos, Swanson Apartments (Great Falls), 1991 (Box-folder 36/25)
  - Order to Provide Information, American Stores, 1990 (Box-folder 36/26)
  - Company, American Stores Properties, and Jewel Companies
  - Order to Provide Information, City of Bozeman, 1990 (Box-folder 36/27)
  - Order for Removal and Clean-up, Lewis Construction (Vaughn, MT), 1990 (Box-folder 36/28)
  - Stipulation, Cobblestone Garage and Machine (Absarokee, MT), 1989 (Box-folder 36/29)
  - Transcripts, Amendments and Adoption of Rules In the Montana Implementation Plan (EPA), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 36/30)
  - Transcripts, American Smelting and Refining (Sulfur Oxide variance), 1975 (Box-folder 36/31)
  - Transcripts, Anaconda Company (Sulfur Oxide, Fluoride and particulate emission variances), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 36/32-34)
  - Transcripts, ASARCO (Lead zinc complex sulfur Oxide emissions), 1976 (Box-folder 36/35)
  - Transcripts, Big West Oil Company (high sulfur Residue fuels), 1974-1975 (Box-folder 36/36)
  - Transcripts, CENEX-EXXON (Hearings on NOVs, Orders to Take Corrective Action), 1976 (Box-folder 36/37)
  - Transcripts, Farmers Union Central Exchange (NOVs), 1976 (Box-folder 36/38)
  - Transcripts, Flint Valley Forest Products, Philipsburg (Variance from rule), 1974 (Box-folder 36/39)
  - Transcripts, Glendive Community Hospital (Order To Take Corrective Action), 1976 (Box-folder 36/40)
  - Transcripts, Montana-Dakota Utilities Company (Variance from rules for emissions of particulate matter from fuel burning), 1975 (Box-folder 36/41)
  - Transcripts, Montana Power Company (Billings) (Steam electric plant), 1974 (Box-folder 36/42)
  - Transcripts, Phillips Petroleum Co. (re: variance For petroleum storage at Great Falls), 1974 (Box-folder 36/43)
  - Transcripts, Stauffer Chemical Co. (re: variances From control of visible/fluoride emissions, particulates), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 36/44-45)
  - Activity Reports, 1984 (Box-folder 37/1)
  - Advisory Councils, General, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 37/2)
  - Advisory Councils, Capital Finance, 1984 (Box-folder 37/3)
  - Advisory Councils, Conservation and Resource Development Division, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 37/4)
  - Advisory Councils, Daly Ditches, 1979 (Box-folder 37/5)
  - Advisory Councils, Legacy Program, 1984 (Box-folder 37/6)
  - Advisory Councils, Low-income Energy Programs, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 37/7)
  - Advisory Councils, Renewable Energy, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 37/8)
  - Advisory Councils, Resources Conservation, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 37/9)
  - Advisory Councils, Soil Survey, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 37/10)
  - Advisory Councils, Water Development, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 37/11)
  - Advisory Councils, Weather Modification, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 37/12)
  - Air Quality Bureau, Montgomery Construction, 1992 (Box-folder 37/13)
  - Air Quality Bureau, Hearings, 1992 (Box-folder 37/14)
  - Board of Health, Meeting Items, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 37/15)
  - Capitol-for-a-Day, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 37/16)
  - “Colstrip 3 and 4, Ash Pond-Sludge Pond”, 1983 (Box-folder 37/17-19)
  - Deputy Director, Darby (Dave), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 37/20)
  - Director, Fasbender (Larry), 1986-1987 (Box-folder 37/21-22)
  - DNRC, Goals and Objectives, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 37/23)
  - Northern Lights, Inc. (Agreement to Waive, Major Facility Siting Act, Kootenai River), 1979-1983 (Box-folder 37/24)
  - Water Resources, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 37/25)
  - Conoco/Kerley, Billings, Permit Appeal (Parts I-VI: Discovery, Briefs, Transcripts, Testimony, Exhibits), 1990 (Box-folder 38/1-8)
  - Noranda Minerals, Montanore Project (Testimony, Exhibits, Public Comments. Includes VHS tape), 1992 (Box-folder 38/9-14)
  - Stillwater Mining Company, Mine at Nye (Petition, Public Notice, Public Comments, Complaint), 1992 (Box-folder 38/15-20)
  - “Air Rules (Testing Permits)”, 1987 (Box-folder 39/1)
  - Anaconda Wastewater Treatment Facilities, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 39/2)
  - ASARCO Exemption (Hearing transcript), 1972 (Box-folder 39/3)
  - (State) Board of Health Meetings, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 39/4-19)
  - Board of Health and Environmental Sciences (BHES) Meetings, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 39/20-21)
  - Contract, DHES and Department of Health and Human Services/Indian Health Service, 1993 (Box-folder 39/22)
  - Environmental Protection Agency, 1974-1982 (Box-folder 39/23)
  - Garlick’s Helicopters Inc. (Investigation of Environmental Conditions), 1993 (Box-folder 40/1)
  - Hearings (includes “Free Care” hearing), 1972 September – November (Box-folder 40/2)
  - Licensure Concurrence, 1971 (Box-folder 40/3)
  - Non-Degradation Hearings, 1992 (Box-folder 40/4)
  - Noranda Minerals, Montanore Project (Exhibits #1-6: Environmental Impact Statement, Petition for Change in Quality of Ambient Waters with Testimony and Supplemental information, App. For Hard Rock Mining Permit), 1992 (Box-folder 40/5-14)
  - Stillwater Mining Company, East Boulder (Pre-hearing comments), 1992 (Box-folder 40/15)
  - Surface Water Quality and Standards, Amendments, 1980, 1982 (Box-folder 40/16-17)
  - Village Water and Sewer Association, Inc. (Sun Prairie Village, Great Falls), 1988 (Box-folder 40/18)
  - Water Quality Standards/Criteria (Transcripts, Public Comments), 1973 (Box-folder 40/19)
  - Yellowstone County Health Department, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 40/20)
  - Yellowstone County, Legal, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 40/21)
  - Anaconda Mining (includes: Variances applications and renewals, Great Western Sugar Co. and Caird Engineering, Environmental Impact Study), 1971-1979 (Box-folder 41/1-13)
  - Anaconda Mining vs. EPA (Deposition transcripts), 1972 (Box-folder 41/14-16)
  - B and T Management Appeal, 1974 (Box-folder 41/17)
  - “The Barge,” Cascade County (transcript), 1974 (Box-folder 41/18)
  - Beaverhead County Landfill (includes photos), 1979 (Box-folder 41/19)
  - Berg Lumber Company (Open Burn permit), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 41/20)
  - Big West Oil Company, Variance (hearings), 1973-1975 (Box-folder 41/21)
  - Billings, Deaconess Hospital (Appeal and Withdrawal), 1978 (Box-folder 41/22)
  - Boehm, Edward (Livingston Convalescent Home), 1975 (Box-folder 41/23)
  - Burlington Northern, 1974, 1978 (Box-folder 41/24)